Email ID: prassan.jha@rediffmail.com

prasannjha1965@gmail.com

Mob: - 8340310147 9386731522



Prasann Kumar Jha

Present Status: State Head (NAVRANG),

Area of Operation – Bihar

Annual Package – 17.13 Lacs,

Expectation -25% hike

Notice Period – 90 days

Team Productivity: - Responsible for Auction of Repossessed Stock through Direct Contacts and Agency (Online /Offline) for Bihar.

Target achieved: - On an average Auction Sale achieved 10 units (1.0 Crore) per month

Date of Birth: - 08/07/1965

Experience: - 30 years in the field of Marketing, Finance & Recovery (more than 26 years in

NBFC)

Products handled/ experience: - Commercial Vehicles, Car, M U V and C E (Funding, Recovery and Liquidation of Stock).

Objective

"To Build and Sustain my career in Financial Services Sector by utilizing myself as a resource for the challenging jobs in this competitive world, thereby upgrading my knowledge & skills"

Professional Experience

Present Job Status

Name of the Organization: Poonawalla Fincorp Limited (Earlier Magma Fincorp Ltd).

Designation : Manager (NAVRANG)

Duration : Since 28/05/2010 Till Date.

Job Profile-:

- Monitoring Auction Activities
- Liasoning with Agencies, Bidders, Direct Clients for Disposal of Stock on Sale,
- Monitoring of Parking Yard,
- Physical Stock Audit and Verification of Documents related to Repossessed Stock in Yard.

- Monitoring Repo. Entry and Release Entry to keep track of actual stock.
- Monitoring Repossession and Release Activity,
- Monitoring and Execution of Auction Sale Process
- Daily Reporting on Auction Activity,
- Monitoring of Documentation of entire Sale Related Docs.
- Monitoring of N O C and RTO related Activities,
- Refurbishment of Repossessed Stock for Price enhancement.
- Resale of refurbished asset to Buyers.
- Lisoning with Recovery and Sales Team for better Price against salable stock.
- Lisoning with Legal Team for Clearance of Legal Stock.

Previous Job Experience

Name of the Organization: TATA MOTORS FINACE LIMITED.

Designation : Manager

Duration : Since 06/11/2006 to 27th May 2010.

Job Profile-:

- To Supervise a Collection Team.
- To Monitor and Supervise Collection Agency.
- Resolving chronic cases.
- To monitor Repossession Agency for Recovery of Asset.
- Monitoring auction for Disposal of Repossessed Assets
- Reporting to Management on Daily Activity,
- Monitoring N O C / RTO on sale of vehicle.

Work Experience

Name of the Organization : Indus Ind Bank Limited

Designation : Area Officer

Duration : From 01.02.1997 to 04.11.2006

Job Profile-:

"My job profile includes to source, analyze and process the proposals of the customers for the Assets viz sales in MUV, CV, CE, Car and Three-wheeler (Auto Rickshaw) Loan and Monitoring Recovery"

Work Experience

•

Name of the Organization : Novapan India Limited

Designation : Sales Officer

Duration : 01/12/1995 to 30/01/1997

<u>Job Profile-:</u> To Sell Novapan particle and Laminated Board through Dealer and Direct Selling, Meeting with Architect and Interior Designer for Sales Promotion.

Work Experience

,

Name of the Organization : Singer India Limited

Designation : Unit Manager

Duration : 02/08/1993 to 20/11/1995

<u>Job Profile-:</u> To Sell Sewing Machine of Merit and Singer Brand along with Home Appliances on Cash and on Hire Purchase also, through a Direct Sales Team and through Retail Sale from Show Room. Monitoring Sales Team ,Show Room Staff and Organizing Sales Campaign.

Work Experience

,

Name of the Organization : Soft Corp Computers Pvt. Limited

Designation : Sales Officer

Duration : From 04.06.1992 to 10.07.1993

<u>Job Profile-:</u> To Sell Computer System and Fax Machine on Cash, through a Direct Selling to Business House, Industrialist and Professionals.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION			
DEGREE	INSTITUTE / UNIVERSTIY	SUBJECTS/DISCIPLINE	Year
Bachelor of Science (Stat. Hons.)	Ranchi University	Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics and Statistics	1987
Intermediate	Ranchi University Ranchi	Physics, Chemistry, Mathematics	1984
X th	Bihar School Examination Board Patna	Arts, Science, Commerce	1981

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

 Post Graduate Diploma in Personnel Management & Industrial Relation from XISS, RANCHI, Period – From 1989 TO 1991.

EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

• Played for Club Cricket Team in Jamshedpur (A – division)

HOBBIES

- Photography
- Listening Music
- Playing Cricket
- Reading Newspapers
- Driving and Travelling
- Pencil Art
- Playing Hawaiian Guitar

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth : 08.07.1965

Age : 57 Years

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Languages Known : English, Hindi, Bangla and Maithili

Nationality : Indian

Permanent Address : S/o Mr. Narendra Kumar Jha

H.No. 349, Road No. – F, Sonari West New Lay Out,

Jamshedpur -831011 (Jharkhand)

Mo - 9386731522, Mo- 8340310147,

Place: Jamshedpur Prasann Kumar Jha

Dated: 16.11.2022

[&]quot;I here by certify that the above-mentioned statements are true to the best of my knowledge and belief"